35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1] [Items 1-3] Carousel number 30 [Items 4-20], 1972 February 15; 11 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Boat on water with mountains in the background], 16
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Children [with their parents] walking on a sidewalk], 17
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Children sitting on a boat on land with their dog], 18
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Teacher teaching young kids], 19
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Boat on water], 20
  - Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2], 1972 February 15; 12 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Man [Dog sledding] mushing], 1
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A building], 2
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snowy mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Drawn picture of a man on a horse leading band of animals and wagons], 4
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Train going over bridge], 5
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Man walking through a forrest], 6
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snowcapped mountains], 7
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Sunset over water], 8
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: American flag and Alaskan flag], 9
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Teacher teaching students], 10
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Alaska's size being compared to the overall size of the U.S.], 11
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Aerial view of land], 12
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: People standing in front of a building], 13
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Sun setting over mountains, a building], 14
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Woman at desk listening to a man holding a book], 15
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Students working in a lab], 16
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A graduation ceremony], 17
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snowcapped mountains], 18
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Body of water iin front of snowcapped mountains], 19
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: People sitting outside, view of mountains in the distance], 20
  - Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2] [Items 1-7] Carousel number 31 [Items 8-12], 1972 February 15; 13 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: School buses lined up, snow on ground, people walking], 1
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A graduation ceremony], 2
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: People listening to a man speak at the podium], 3
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A building], 4
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A woman reading from a book to people sitting outside of a building], 5
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: A building], 6
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snowy mountains], 7
    - Beginning of Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals] [: Man sitting inside of a house], 8
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man standing outside of a small tent, mountains in the background], 9
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Woman sitting on a bench, eating something], 10
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small tents set up on snowy ground], 11
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small tents set up on snowy ground [with people skiiing]], 12
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 14 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man sitting on a raft on land, looking in his boot], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Body of water, mountains ahead], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small tents set up near mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snowy mountains], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Sun shining through clouds], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small tents set up on snowy ground], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Two men sitting in a raft with supplies], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small group of people sitting on a raft on land for a pciture], 8
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 15 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man wearing sunglasses holding a scrap of metal], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snowy hills], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Body of water near mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men sitting on rock ledge], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Woman wearing special goggles, near camera equipment], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Person walking in the far off distance], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men eating outside], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man and woman with camera equipment], 8
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 16 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: People holding skiis, sitting on rocks], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small shack set up by mountains], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Close-up of a man], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Three people around supplies in snow], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man on skiis on a mountain], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man on skiis on a mountain], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man laying on a rock], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Close-up of a husky in front of sled], 8
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 17 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man standing outside of a shack], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Rocks], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Two men sitting on a rock], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man sitting in a tent], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Boat on land], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man holding a ski], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small camp set up on snow], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man working with camera equipment], 8
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 18 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man with camera equipment], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man skiing], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Three men leaning against rocks with skiis], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snow on mountain], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man skiing], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Three men leaning against rocks], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Camp set up on snow], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snow], 8
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men outside of shack], 9
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Sleeping husky], 10
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Dusk on mountain top], 11
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 19 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Laundry hanging between tents], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Small body of water on mountaintop], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man skiing], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Camp set up on snow], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men shoveling], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men skiing], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Food supplies stuck in snow], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Reader's Digest magazines], 8
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snow on ground], 9
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snow on mountain], 10
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Boat in small pool of water by mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Husky sitting on snow], 12
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men skiing], 13
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Men skiing], 14
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Woman sitting on bench eating], 15
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Man skiing], 16
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Camp set up on mountain], 17
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Boat on land], 18
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Dog lying by food dish], 19
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Building], 20
  - Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals], undated; 20 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Water on moutaintop], 1
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Boat on land], 2
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Boat on land], 3
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Dog lying by food dish], 4
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Dog lying by food dish], 5
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Snow on top of mountain], 6
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: View of mountains behind pine trees], 7
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Waterfall], 8
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Pine trees, mountain in background], 9
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountaintop], 10
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountain], 11
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Waterfall], 12
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Waterfall], 13
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountains], 14
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountaintop behind fog], 15
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountains], 16
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: A husky on snow], 17
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: A mountain behind pine trees], 18
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Mountains], 19
    - [Carousel number 31 [Mount Rainier mountain climbing and skiing expedition with unidentified individuals]: Parked cars], 20
  Box 1590
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 32 [New Guinea], circa 1969; 1 (Box 1590)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 32 [New Guinea] [: People filming Lowell Thomas sitting on steps talking with another man], 1
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Woman holding camera, standing next to Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man holding a camera], 3
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People with camera equipment], 4
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People with camera equipment], 5
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man holding a camera], 6
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives of New Guinea sitting], 7
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People with camera equipment, talking with natives], 8
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People with camera equipment, talking with natives], 9
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives wearing headdresses and skirts, Lowell Thomas talking with people by the camera], 10
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Two natives shaking hands], 11
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Person working behind camera], 12
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man holding camera], 13
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives in hut], 14
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People with camera equipment, talking with natives], 15
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native observing camera], 16
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives talking with camera crew], 17
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man behind camera], 18
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives in a hut], 19
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Two people looking at camera equipment], 20
  - Carousel number 32 [New Guinea], circa 1969; 2 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Two natives sitting on a log], 1
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Three natives in a forest], 2
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Line of natives holding spears, man working with camera equipment], 3
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People working with camera equipment], 4
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People under a tent working with camera equipment], 5
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Men with camera equipment], 6
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man], 7
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man], 8
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Two men standing together, talking], 9
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native looking out], 10
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native man sitting on dirt], 11
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Three native men standing near a hut], 12
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Clay artwork], 13
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives and camera man forging river], 14
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Fog settling over mountains], 15
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Clay scultpure], 16
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man painted with clay, clay mask on top of his head], 17
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Clay mask], 18
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives working through tall grass], 19
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives by hut], 20
  - Carousel number 32 [New Guinea], circa 1969; 3 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Men workign with camera equipment], 1
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Men from camera crew gathered with natives], 2
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man holding camera equipment, natives sitting on the ground behind him], 3
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man holding a camera], 4
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Natives wearing clay mask, putting on a performance], 5
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: People working with camera equipment], 6
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Men working with camera equipment underneath a tent], 7
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man working with camera equipment], 8
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas sitting on steps with another man, people filming with camera], 9
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Fog settling over mountains], 10
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Fog settling over mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man], 12
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native man leaning against a hut], 13
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Man with camera and natives forging a river], 14
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native man looking out from door of hut], 15
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man's face], 16
    - [Carousel number 32 [New Guinea]: Native man painting a piece of wood], 17
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 4 (Box 1590)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea] [Lowell Thomas talking with a woman], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing with a woman holding a [koala bear?] dog], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient Greecian building], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas sitting on a ledge that overlooks ocean], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient ruins], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman standing on a busy street in front of an ancient building], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ruined building], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing in a building], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: View from ancient building, city ahead], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient building], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large city], 11